## **Connor Musson**

Software Engineer

mussonconnor@gmail.com | UK/USA | https://www.linkedin.com/in/connor-musson/

https://github.com/cmusson 🕜 https://connormusson.vercel.app/

#### **₽** Profile

I am a dual US/UK citizen, a passionate, dedicated individual, experienced in high level Software Engineering. I work well independently and also in a team, collaborating and communicating effectively. With many years experience working to meet company requirements as well as those set by clients or vendors.

## Skills

Javascript | TypeScript/TS | Next | React | Remix | React-Native | HTML | CSS | Tailwind | Redux | Storybook | Jest | Git | Node | React Flow | Leadership | Teamwork | Communication | Collaboration

# Professional Experience

07/2024 – present Dallas, USA (Remote) **Frontend Engineer - CrateBind,** (*TS, Next, Tailwind, React Flow, Redux, React Native*) CrateBind builds apps and websites for clients.

A small team where my work included:

- Improved and integrated features into an early-stage AI/React-Flow app
- Created a second NextJS application in relation to the project
- Rapidly gained React-Flow expertise and executed significant improvements
- Built a React Native Expo mobile application from scratch

04/2024 – 06/2024 London, UK **Frontend Engineer - Borderless,** (TS, Next, Tailwind, Storybook)

Part of a two person team building the new FE from scratch, where my work included:

- Building out the initial three web app frontends in Next, with TS and TailwindCSS
- Setting up redux and global state management in the apps
- Building out the Storybook component library for reusable components
- Developing the frontend style-guide
- Using prettier and linting best practices to ensure conformity across the codebase

02/2022 – 09/2023 Adelaide, Australia (Remote) Frontend Engineer - Fluidity, (TS, Next, Remix, React, Storybook) ☑

Fluidity rewards users for swapping, trading or transacting assets on the blockchain. A small team where my responsibilities included:

- Improving the inherited beta codebase
- Leading, planning, architecting and building the current website from scratch (Next)
- Contributing to building the web3 app, working with a new framework (Remix)
- Built a component library using Storybook

2021 Barcelona, Spain **Fullstack Engineer - MyPLaces,** (TS, React Native, Express, Node, PostgreSQL, Redux) A mobile app where users can set up a profile with their recommendations of various places around the world.

A 5-member team where my responsibilities included:

- Setting up a Node Express backend server
- Creating a relational database in postgreSQL
- Working with the frontend team to build key features

09/2019 - present

International Travel (Solo), Backpacking/Digital Nomad

SE Asia, Americas and Central Europe - Radically developed my communication skills, became more independent and self driven, transcending cultural boundaries.

### **Education**

2021 Barcelona, Spain **Software Engineering,** *Codeworks* 

A software engineering, full-stack web development school. The program covers HTML, CSS, JavaScript, Node, Express, SQL and NoSQL databases, Angular, and React, DevOps, continuous deployment and systems architecture.

09/2011 – 07/2014 Manchester, UK Bachelor's Degree, Mechanical Engineering, 1st Class (Hons),

The Manchester Metropolitan University

Graduated with Honours in BEng Mechanical Engineering, Achieving 1st class score (4.0 GPA). Accredited by both the IMechE and IET.